Hello friends,
you are very welcome to Market Production.  Friends,
in this video we will talk about the quarter one results of ICICI LBD.   Please
subscribe to the channel.  If you like it then
like the video.  Come on friends, let us
move on to the company's update where there is
any dividend
announcement or any major update from the company or
not.  So here, if we talk about
dividend first, then
we are not getting to see any news related to dividend here.
So here in ICICI LBAT,
currently it is a general insurance company.
If you look at it, there is no
big news from the company at present
where the company is giving you dividend or
any big bonus or there is any
news about split.  Ok?  Now let's talk about the
total income of the company,
friends, here you can see the total
income of the company last year,
here you can see the amount which is in lakhs.
So here we will talk in crores.
So the total income last year was Rs 5351 crore
which has increased to Rs 683 crore.  So here the
total income of the company is seen increasing.
If you look at it quarter to quarter, the
total income in the last quarter was Rs 5851 crore,
which has increased to Rs 683 crore.
So the income of the company is seen increasing at very good levels.  If
we talk about total expenses,
if you look at the total expenses of last year, the
total expenses of the company were around Rs 4850 crore, which this time has
increased to Rs 5429 crore as per the sales.  So
according to this, the total income of the company is
seen increasing here.
Along with that, the company's expenses are also
seen increasing accordingly.  Now
friends, let us talk about the tax expenses of the company here. The
tax expenses
are managed in the same way as the
sales growth of the company has been seen increasing here.
Now friends, let us talk
about the profit of the company here, where after
tax, if we look here, then in the net profit of the company,
what increase or decrease will be seen here, let
us see that a little bit.  So you can see
here the profit of the company, the
profit of the company was
580 crores last year, which this
time is 747 crores, the total profit is
seen here, after tax the
profit of the company is 747 crores,
which in the last quarter of last year, the
profit here was 59 crores.
So here the profit of the company is
seen increasing at the rate of approximately 25%.  Here the
company had given you dividend at that time.
But here on the final dividend, the
company has announced to give a dividend of ₹7,
which
you will get to see here in the upcoming dividend,
you can see it in the coming quarters.
So let's just
talk about the share on earnings based on face value.
So here if we talk about earnings per
share, let's go down a little bit.
If you look at the earnings per share of the company,
if you look at the earnings per share, last time it was
around 3.20 and 3.60 is seen here now.
So,
we are seeing good results of the company here
and if seen normally, the earnings per
share was earlier at 11 points.  This
time it is seen around 15 points.
Secondly, according to the face value, the
earnings per share of the company here
seems to be managed quite well.
Thank you.  Like and subscribe.